
export const Questions=[
    {
        id:1,
        question:"What is the addition of 2+4 ?",
        options:[4,5,6,8],
        answer:6
     },
     {
        id:2,
        question:"What is the Substration of 4-1 ?",
        options:[4,5,3,8],
        answer:3
     },
     {
        id:3,
        question:"What is the multiplication of 6*4 ?",
        options:[24,33,56,42],
        answer:24
     },
     {
        id:4,
        question:"What is the Factorial of 4 ?",
        options:[4,24,42,16],
        answer:24
     },
     {
        id:5,
        question:"What is the Division of 8/2 ?",
        options:[4,5,6,8],
        answer:4
     },
     {
        id:6,
        question:"What is the Squre of 11 ?",
        options:[212,121,221,112],
        answer:121
     },
     {
        id:7,
        question:"What is the root of 144 ?",
        options:[11,12,21,13],
        answer:12
     },
     {
        id:8,
        question:"What is the Quabe of 3 ?",
        options:[9,27,87,11],
        answer:27
     },
     {
        id:9,
        question:"What is the  Multiplication of 2*6*7 ?",
        options:[84,49,48,86],
        answer:84
     },
     {
        id:10,
        question:"What is the factorial of 8 ?",
        options:[40320,40330,40230,40310],
        answer:40320
     }
]

